export const mockResponseCategory = {
  "trivia_categories": [
    {
      "id": 9,
      "name": "General Knowledge"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "name": "Entertainment: Books"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "name": "Entertainment: Film"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "name": "Entertainment: Music"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "name": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "name": "Entertainment: Television"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "name": "Entertainment: Video Games"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "name": "Entertainment: Board Games"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "name": "Science & Nature"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "name": "Science: Computers"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "name": "Science: Mathematics"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "name": "Mythology"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "name": "Sports"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "name": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "name": "History"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "name": "Politics"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "name": "Art"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "name": "Celebrities"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "name": "Animals"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "name": "Vehicles"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "name": "Entertainment: Comics"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "name": "Science: Gadgets"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "name": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "name": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations"
    }
  ]
}
export const mockResponseQuestion = {
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20James%20Dean%27s%20character%20in%20the%201955%20movie%20%22Rebel%20Without%20a%20Cause%22%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Jim%20Stark",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ned%20Stark",
        "Jim%20Kane",
        "Frank%20Stark"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Assyrian%20kings%20did%20NOT%20rule%20during%20the%20Neo-Assyrian%20Empire%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Shamshi-Adad%20III",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Shalmaneser%20V",
        "Esharhaddon",
        "Ashur-nasir-pal%20II"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "In%20Forza%20Motorsport%206%2C%20which%20of%20these%20track-exclusive%20cars%20was%20NOT%20featured%20in%20the%20game%2C%20either%20originally%20with%20the%20game%20or%20added%20as%20DLC%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Aston%20Martin%20Vulcan",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ferrari%20FXX-K",
        "McLaren%20P1%20GTR",
        "Lotus%20E23"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20of%20these%20game%20franchises%20were%20made%20by%20Namco%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Tekken",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Street%20Fighter",
        "Mortal%20Kombat",
        "Dragon%20Quest"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Vehicles",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which%20one%20of%20the%20following%20is%20NOT%20a%20sub-company%20of%20the%20Volkswagen%20Group%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Opel",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Porsche",
        "Bugatti",
        "Bentley"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General%20Knowledge",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In%20which%20fast%20food%20chain%20can%20you%20order%20a%20Jamocha%20Shake%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Arby%27s",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "McDonald%27s",
        "Burger%20King",
        "Wendy%27s"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20Japanese%20music%20group%20was%20formed%20to%20produce%20theme%20music%20for%20the%20anime%20%22Guilty%20Crown%22%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Egoist",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Goose%20house",
        "Babymetal",
        "Garnidelia"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Musicals%20%26%20Theatres",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The%20World%20Chess%20Championship%20in%20Chess%2C%20Act%201%20is%20set%20in%20which%20Italian%20city%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Merano",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Venice",
        "Milan",
        "Rome"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "What%20was%20the%20first%20organic%20compound%20to%20be%20synthesized%20from%20inorganic%20compounds%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Urea",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Propane",
        "Ethanol",
        "Formaldehyde"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who%20is%20the%20second%20person%20to%20take%20up%20the%20mantle%20of%20Night%20Owl%20in%20the%20Watchmen%20graphic%20novel%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Daniel%20Dreiberg",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Nelson%20Gardner",
        "Hollis%20Mason",
        "Adrian%20Veidt"
      ]
    }
  ]
}